Amanda Reilly

amanda@amandareilly.me 619-739-1419 San Diego, CA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

Full stack developer with a passion for puzzle-solving and the skill to write clean, testable, modular code. Experience with MERN stack, and ready and willing to dive head-first into any tech stack and keep at it until there's nothing more to learn (so, forever).

SKILLS

Intermediate: PHP, Gulp, MySQL

Advanced: Mongoose, React, jQuery, Git, GitHub, NPM, SASS, Handlebars, TDD with Enzyme

Proficient: JavaScript (ES6), Node.js, MongoDB, TDD with Mocha and Chai, HTML5, CSS3, REST APIs

Expert: Written & verbal communication, project management, business systems design

EXPERIENCE

RECENT PROJECTS
FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

San Diego, CA April 2018 - Present

<u>YouQuity</u>: A MERN-stack app to help small businesses manage their equity structures little attorney oversight.

<u>Purchaser</u>: A full-stack app to help small businesses manage their purchasing system. Built with NodeJs, HTML, CSS, and jQuery.

ANIMAL CELL THERAPIES, INC.

OPERATIONS MANAGER

San Diego, CA

September, 2014 to Present

- Implemented and managed transition from a single inbound phone line to an in-house multi-line PBX system, saving the company 95% on annual phone costs vs purchasing multiple inbound lines from the telecom vendor. Managed day-to-day operation and troubleshooting of PBX system.
- Implemented and documented new processes for HR management, including transition from manual record keeping to an online HRIS with an employee self-service component, saving approximately 25 man-hours per week.
- Streamlined and modernized legacy operations processes to reduce paper documentation and increase record-keeping consistency.
- Worked with the Director of Quality to design and implement a document management system that
 met the regulatory requirements without being excessively cumbersome for a company of seven
 people.

REILLY COMPUTERS

San Diego, CA

TECHNICIAN

July 2012 to September 2014

- Helped small business and home clients make appropriate technology decisions based on their budgets and needs.
- Set up and configured a new network and server for a small business client, and helped them implement its use in their daily work.
- Conducted troubleshooting and repair sessions for small business and home users.

25TH HOUR ASSISTANTS

Lafayette, IN / San Diego, CA January 2008 to September 2012

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER / VIRTUAL ASSISTANT

- Developed and deployed Wordpress-based websites for small business owners.
- Integrated 3rd-party plugins into Wordpress sites.

EDUCATION

THINKFUL FULL STACK FLEX

December 2018

- Learned industry best practices and practical software development standards with a focus on HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, React, Redux, and algorithms & data structures.
- Created and deployed mobile-first applications while learning new languages and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior web developer.